We are continuously bombarded by
我们不断地被
light, photons.
光子轰击。
And what's quite incredible is that a part of your brain, which is the retina,
令人难以置信的是，您大脑的一部分，也就是视网膜，
is capable of contacting the smallest
能够接触到最小的
possible particle of light, that is, a photon.
光粒子，也就是光子。
The eye, we will see that it has a very great activity at the level of...
我们将看到，眼睛在大脑层面具有非常高的活跃度……
cerebral, that it is even an exteriorized brain, it is an expansion
它甚至是一个外化的脑，是您大脑的
of your brain.
延伸。
And we will see that this eye will naturally have an importance at the level of the static of
我们将看到，这只眼睛自然地对您颈部的静态平衡具有重要性，因此它将直接影响您的重心。
your neck, it will therefore directly influence your center of gravity.
因此，眼睛既影响您的重心，
And so the eye, at the same time it influences your center of gravity, and at the same time your
又影响您的
center
重心。
of gravity influences the eye. So the eye is in fact the lighthouse of all the facials. Ocular tensions, which we see in our consultations, are often related to the liver.
重心反过来也影响眼睛。
to the liver.
肝脏有关。
Whether it's a red eye or a yellow eye,
无论是红眼还是黄眼，
they are a hepatic expression.
它们都是肝脏的表达。
The heart too, there is an important thing,
心脏也很重要，
it is that already in embryology,
因为在胚胎学中，
the eye will come to rest
眼睛会附着在
on the heart.
心脏上。
And it will receive
它将接收
a rhythmic information,
节律信息，
like the throat, that is to say
就像喉咙一样，也就是
your voice, and like
您的声音，以及
the hands. Already, the information
双手。您的双手信息，
of your hands, the information
您的眼睛信息，
of your eyes, the information
您的声音信息，
of your voice are already
这些都是已经存在的
electrical charges,
电荷，
magnetic,
磁荷，
electromagnetic.
电磁荷。
You work
您用
you work with your eyes.
您的眼睛工作。
We can
我们可以
hypnotize someone, you see,
催眠某人，您看，
by voice. Be careful,
通过声音。注意，
I'm talking.
我正在说话。
these frequencies in fact because they are electric fields so same thing with your hands, same
这些频率实际上是因为它们是电场，所以你的手也是一样，
thing with the eyes. But in fact what happens is that we modify
眼睛也是一样。但实际上发生的是我们改变了
alpha frequencies,
阿尔法频率，
you see all these brain frequencies which are also important phenomena of stabilization,
你看，所有这些脑电波频率也是重要的稳定现象，
but in fact the eye already receives information from the heart, from the primary
但实际上眼睛已经接收到了来自心脏的信息，来自
heart, from the good heart. Buddhists
原始心脏，来自好的心脏。佛教徒
They say there is a small invisible thread that connects the heart and
他们说有一根看不见的细线连接着心脏和
the eyes.
眼睛。
Do this exercise of looking at me with your heart.
请做这个练习，用你的心来看我。
Really make that connection.
真正地建立这种连接。
To change and look at me like that.
改变并这样看着我。
And you will see that something will change in the eye.
你会看到眼睛上会有一些变化。
There is a geometry.
有一种几何形状。
The geometry of the smile.
微笑的几何形状。
These are very subtle geometric changes.
这些是非常微妙的几何变化。
to look with the heart.
用心去看。
Because a word, a gesture, a look
因为一句话，一个手势，一个眼神
blocks someone for a lifetime.
会困住一个人一辈子。
But a word, a gesture, a look,
但一句话，一个手势，一个眼神，
if it is placed at the right time,
如果它在正确的时间，
the right space,
正确的空间，
with the right mental image,
带着正确的心理意象，
can free someone.
可以解放一个人。
But for that, you need to have the right timing.
但为此，必须把握好时机。
Here, we want to be recognized,
我们希望被认可，
to be able to emerge from that.
以便能够从中解脱出来。
Same thing with your hands, and same thing with your voice.
你的手也是一样，你的声音也是一样。
This is about attention, because if we want to work on vision,
这是注意力，因为如果我们想训练视力，
we must learn to be attentive.
我们必须学会专注。
So attention is a tool that we must sharpen.
所以注意力是我们必须磨砺的工具。
The kidneys will modify your vision, your perception of reality, through fear.
肾脏会因为恐惧而改变你的视力，你对
reality.
现实的感知。
Fear can completely change it.
恐惧可以完全改变它。
We lose like anger, you see, boom, I change my reality.
我们失去的就像愤怒一样，你看，啪，我改变了我的现实。
Initially, anger is a force of clairvoyance.
最初，愤怒是一种洞察力。
But at the moment when anger arises, if you are attentive,
但当愤怒出现时，如果你注意，
there is a clarity.
会有一种清晰。
We see the fault.
我们看到了错误。
The work will be an embryology work, an anatomy work,
这项工作将是胚胎学工作，解剖学工作，
a work of functional studies and then a slightly more spiritual work on the eye.
功能研究工作，以及对眼睛进行更具精神性的工作。
So we're going to work a little bit on what we call the differences.
所以我们将稍微研究一下我们所说的差异。
which are important because it will give us what we call the world of perception,
这很重要，因为它将给我们带来我们所说的感知世界，
the world of sensation, the world of volition, the world of consciousness.
感觉世界，意志世界，意识世界。
But learning to be able to gradually distinguish between perhaps
但是要学会逐渐区分可能
the illusion that may appear there.
出现的幻觉。
It's not easy because we very quickly have what we call prejudices.
这并不容易，因为我们很快就会有我们所说的偏见。
So there, he is confident.
所以他很自信。
That means he will undergo his environment, the totality of his environment.
这意味着他将屈服于他的环境，他的整个环境。
And in fact, it is there before the bone.
事实上，他在骨骼之前就在那里。
So it will be the soft that will control the hard. It will have laws, laws of position, laws of mobility, laws of information integration. And then, we will also have to understand this purely neurosensory level of the eye, this pathway of neuromotor involvement that we will study, because we will still study neurophysiology.
所以软组织将控制硬组织。
this pathway of neuromotor involvement that we will study, because we will still study neurophysiology.
我们将研究的神经运动参与途径，因为我们仍然会研究神经生理学。
We will still go into a little detail from the moment we touch
我们将从我们接触眼睛的那一刻起，深入研究
the eye,
眼睛，
where a photon will touch the eye, everything that will happen.
当一个光子接触眼睛时，所有将发生的事情。
From your conjunctiva, your cornea, all these liquids that it will touch, boom,
从你的结膜，你的角膜，所有这些液体都将接触到，
and it will at some point perform a transduction.
然后它将在某个时刻进行转导。
So it will change this light into electricity.
所以它将把光线转化为电能。
And then it will go into the lateral geniculate body.
然后它将进入外侧膝状体。
So it will go into a part of your brain.
所以它将进入你大脑的一部分。
which will be completely influenced in the whole system of papillae,
它将完全受到整个帕佩茨系统（Papez system）的影响，
we will see, and then with the olivary nuclei, the pulvinar, all that will be integrated,
我们将看到，然后与橄榄核、丘脑枕等一起整合，
to go towards a radiation on the occipital areas,
然后辐射到枕叶区域，
which will transmit another information to us,
这将给我们传递另一个信息，
that is to say that we lose 80% of reality.
也就是说，我们失去了80%的现实。
Already in our way of seeing, that's crazy,
在我们的观察方式中，这已经很疯狂了，
that is to say that we are very strongly influenced by our experience.
也就是说，我们深受我们经历的影响。
We will lose 80%.
我们将失去80%。
It's almost organized.
这几乎是有组织的。
We will always be in a mechanism of interpretation.
我们将始终处于一种解释机制中。
And as soon as there is emotion, as soon as there are stories that are lived, we will see things again
一旦有情感，一旦有经历过的故事，我们就会重新看待事物，
like that.
就像这样。
And so it will be important little by little to dare to be curious.
因此，逐渐敢于好奇将很重要。
And so the goal as an osteopath will be to be able to receive this information,
因此，作为一名整骨医生，目标是能够接收这些信息，
of environmental type too, because we will not only look at one thing,
也包括环境类型的信息，因为我们不会只看
one thing,
一件事，
but also this facial level.
还有这个筋膜层面。
So treating the eye is treating the whole body.
所以治疗眼睛就是治疗整个身体。
But to treat the eye, you must first treat the whole body.
但要治疗眼睛，首先要治疗整个身体。
We can say that the eye is like a kind of balance
我们可以说眼睛就像一种平衡
between a structure in which it is integrated
在它所整合的结构之间
and the problem that can be expressed.
以及可能表达出来的问题。
So it will be a balance.
所以它将是一个平衡。